outletinn.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy policy. outletinn, online deals gear and deals equipment shop

1\. LEGAL INFORMATION

**Website:** www.outletinn.com

 **Company that owns:** Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. ([www.tradeinn.com](http://www.tradeinn.com/ "tradeinn"))

 **Company Adress:** C/ Pirineus, 9, 17460 Celrà (Girona), Spain. 

**Managing Director:** David Martin Gaya 

**Commercial Register:** Registre mercantil de Girona - tomo 1123 / folio 108 / hoja GI20086 - Inscripción 1ª

**VAT identification number:** ESB17527524

**Legally responsible for the content of this website:** David Martin Gaya

2\. DATA PROTECTION

Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. is committed to protecting your privacy. We inform you that the personal data you provide will be processed in order to provide the services and / or to deliver the requested products if you make a purchase, and in order to facilitate, even by electronic means, commercial information. 

The responsible for these treatments is Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. with registered office at C/ Pirineus, 9, 17460 Celrà (Girona), Spain. Phone: +34 93 220 00 89. 

The data protection delegate of Tradeinn (DPD) is Mrs. Ester Salvador Ibáñez, this is the person you can contact to exercise your rights. You can contact the data protection delegate of Tradeinn (DPD) through the following electronic address: lopd@tradeinn.com. 

The legal basis of the treatment in case you are a client is the execution of the contract in which you are a party. 

The legal basis of the commercial information is your express consent, because when you register, you give your express authorization for us to send you commercial information, including by electronic means. 

Whenever you wish, you can unsubscribe from our newsletter and revoke this express consent, to stop receiving this type of email. To do this, you can unsubscribe at any time, via the My Account section or by clicking the unsubscribe link available in all promotional emails sent by Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. 

When you sign up, you agree to provide us with valid personal data that allows the provision of the service by Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. and your correct identification as a registered user. These personal data that you must provide us are essential to send the information and / or the orders and the preparation of the invoices. 

The absence of these data or their inaccuracy will lead to the impossibility to send information and / or delivery of orders. If an order can not be delivered for this reason, it will be automatically cancelled. 

Only Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. will be responsible for the user´s personal data. The data you provided are stored in a file owned by Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. that complies with current regulations on data protection. 

Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. undertakes to comply with the duty of secrecy of such data, as well as to treat them with confidentiality, assuming the necessary measures to avoid alteration, loss, treatment or unauthorized access, as set out in Regulation (EU) 2016 / 679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016. 

Also, Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. undertakes not to use such personal data for purposes other than the purpose of the service provided through its websites or commercial bulletins, which offer information on product offers for direct sale through the Internet and non-transmission of them to third parties, unless they necessarily intervene in the execution of the object of the contract. 

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you give your express consent so that your personal data may be communicated and / or transferred internationally to other companies of the group or to affiliated companies of Tradeinn Retail Services SL, for the purposes stated in the previous paragraphs. 

In the same way, you expressly consent to the transfer and / or international transfer of your data to companies with whom it is necessary to share them for the successful completion of the order or the sending of information, such as transport companies, parcel companies, messaging, payment, logistics, professional hosting services and data management, online chat providers, web analytics services, etc. You are informed that your data may be or will be transferred to these companies. 

This consent may be revoked at any time by means of a signed document with the reference 'REVOCATION OF CONSENT', addressed to Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. 

In addition, you have the right to access the information we have about you, to rectify it, to suppress it, to oppose your treatment, to request the limitation of the treatment or to request the portability of your data. For this, you only need to communicate it by means of a signed document, enclosing a photocopy of any valid official document that proves your identity, addressed to: TRADEINN RETAIL SERVICES S.L. C / Pirineus, 9. 17460 Celrà. Girona - Spain; Or by email to lopd@tradeinn.com. 

In addition, we inform you that you also have the right to file a claim with a control authority, such as the Spanish Agency for data protection.

3\. COPYRIGHT

Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. has exclusive rights over the entire content and the use of the our stores website, graphics, images, texts, logos, GIFs and icons with the exception of trademarks, logos or content relating to shops or listed products. All reproduction, distribution, modification, retransmission or publication of these elements is strictly forbidden without the prior written accord of the company Tradeinn Retail Services S.L.

4\. COOKIES

We use our own and third party cookies to provide a better service to our customers and to offer you information and advertising that is of your interest. If you continue browsing, we consider that you accept its use. You can always configure your browser so that cookies are not registered. You can find how to do it on this page.

\- What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer when visiting a website. This text file stores information that can be read by the website when visiting it again at a later date. Some of these cookies are necessary, otherwise the site is unable to work properly. These small text files are associated to an anonymous user without the possibility of deducing personal data from it. These cookies do not contain confidential information that identifies you personally. In general these files are associated to the identifier of a device (IP), but not to a specific user, so the personal data cannot be deduced.

\- Type and purpose of cookies:

Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. uses cookies to help us provide you with a better user experience based on your personal preferences. By using cookies Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. makes sure that you do not receive or need to enter the same information every single time you visit the Tradeinn websites. Cookies are also used to optimize the performance of the websites. For example, cookies make the checkout process easier or help you to find a specific item of clothing faster. 

The list below provides more details about what cookies we use: 

Own cookies are those that are sent to the user´s computer from computers managed by Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. and from which the service requested by the user is provided. 

Third party cookies are those that are sent to the user´s computer from a computer that is not managed by Tradeinn Retail Services S.L., such as a social network. 

We collect browsing data in a non-anonymous way in order to analyze the information collected from your browser and to improve your browsing experience in our stores. 

We use local storage cookies, PHPSESSID, SERVERID, _atuvc, barra_cookies, cookie_cart, cookie_cart_total, datos transporte, nospeeder and tradenewsletter. These cookies are needed for the site to work. Without them you won´t be able to add items to your cart or checkout. 

The site uses its own personalization cookies that allow the user to set elements such as the language or country of delivery so they can have a better browsing experience. 

The site uses measurement cookies that allow us to perform the measurement and statistical analysis of the use made by users of our service. Your navigation is analyzed through our website in order to improve the product offer and the service. 

The site also uses Google Analytics and Google Adwords cookies, specifically cookies _utma, _utmb, _utmc and _utmz. This is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ('Google' from now on). Google Analytics and Google Adwords use cookies, which are small data files that are stored on your computer and that help the web analyze how users use it. These cookies allow the website to remember information about your visit, such as your preferred language or the country of delivery, which may facilitate your next visit and make the web more useful to you. The information generated by the cookies on your use of the website (including the IP address) will be transmitted and stored by Google on its servers. Google will use this information in order to evaluate the use of the website, make reports on the activity of the website and provide other services related to the web activity on the internet. Google will not associate your IP address with any other information that Google may have. For more information you can consult the page www.google.com/intl/es/analytics/privacyoverview.html 

\- How can I disable cookies?

You can modify your browser to turn off cookies. This is very easy to do. Please note: if you disable cookies, your user name and password will no longer be stored on any website. Depending on which web browser you use it is possible to control how cookies are used, or to delete existing cookies from your computer. You can find instructions on how to control the use of cookies, or delete cookies from your computer at http://www.aboutcookies.org (English only).

Firefox: (https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) 

Google Chrome: (https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) 

Internet Explorer: (https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) 

Safari: (https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_GB&locale=en_GB)

5\. FACEBOOK SOCIAL PLUGINS

Our website uses social plugins ('Plugins') of Facebook.com social network, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plugins are marked with a Facebook logo or with the words 'Facebook social Plugin'.

If you visit one of our websites, which contains such a plugin, your internet browser connects directly to the servers of Facebook. The content of the Plugin is transferred directly to your browser and is integrated to the website. Therefore, Tradeinn Retail Services S.L. has no influence on the treatment of the data that Facebook makes through this supplement and we inform you as we know.

By integrating the plugin, Facebook receives the information that a corresponding website of ours has been viewed. If you are logged into Facebook, Facebook can assign your visit to your account. If you interact with the plugins, for example you confirm the 'Like' button or make a comment, the corresponding information from your browser is sent directly to Facebook and saved there as well.

To find out the purpose and extent of the collection of data, the further processing and usage of your data by Facebook as well as your rights and possible settings in this regard to protect your privacy please consider the privacy statement of Facebook.
